wonderfulengineering.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy

Thank You for seeing us. The privacy of our visitors at Wonderfulengineering.com is important to us.

At Wonderful engineering, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Wonderful engineering, and how we safeguard your information. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Personal Information**  
As with most other websites, we collect the data you provide to us when you visit or post a comment to our site. This information may include your name, your email address, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Your personal information will never be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals to anyone.

 **Cookies**  
We also use third party advertisements on Wonderful engineering to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Wonderful engineering readers based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
**Ads**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
